William Tjang

Phone: +61 430 999 617

Email: william.tj29@gmail.com
Website: https://twillij.github.io/

I am a graduate programmer who is actively looking for opportunities where I can utilise my skills and challenge myself to become a better programmer. I have 2 years of experience with C++ and C# and have applied them to several game projects (including VR) using Unity and Unreal Engine.

Technical Skills

Programming C++, C#, HTML/CSS

Game Engine Unity, Unreal Engine

Version Control Git with GitHub and GitKraken

Project Management Trello, HacknPlan

MS Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

Other Skills

Technical support

Customer service

Teaching

Multilingual – English, Indonesian,

Japanese

Problem solving

Communication

Teamwork

• Leadership

• Work ethic

Work Experience

Game Programmer @ JBK Studios

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020

Developed a game using hybrid C++ and blueprint programming in Unreal Engine 4

IT Support Staff @ National Institute of Dramatic Arts (NIDA)

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

Served as level 1-2 IT support for students and staffs within the Kensington campus

Finance Officer @ Rider & Bell Group

Jul 2018 - Oct 2019

Performed various financial affairs tasks including general bookkeeping, service delivery management and purchasing management, along with occasional tasks such as low-level IT support and website maintenance

Private Tutor @ Ezy Math Tutoring

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

Worked as a contractor for a tutoring agency which required me to prepare my own content

Education

Academy of Interactive Entertainment	2019 - 2020
Advanced Diploma of Game Programming	
University of New South Wales	2014 - 2018
Bachelor of Economics	
Caringbah High School	2008 - 2013
Higher School Certificate	

Referees

Rick Ko	Venkat Ravilla
Project Lead	Systems Architect, ICT manager
JBK Studios	National Institute of Dramatic Arts (NIDA)

Contact details are available upon request